atlantichealth.org 2018-11-23

# Website Privacy Policy - Atlantic Health

At Atlantic Health System, we are committed to maintaining your trust. We have created this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain how we collect, use, protect and share information that we collect from you on Atlantichealth.org and its related websites, and any online feature, service and/or program offered by Atlantic Health System (collectively, our “Site”). We encourage you to review the entirety of this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not understand any aspects of our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at [info@atlantichealth.org](mailto:info@atlantichealth.org). By accessing and/or otherwise using our Site, you acknowledge that the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy apply to you. If you do not agree with any term provided in this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use the Site.

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you as a result of your use of our Site. It is not applicable to any information collected by us offline or through any other means, and does not apply to any other web pages, mobile applications, social media sites, email lists, technical and browsing information, and personal information collected and/or owned by any entity other than Atlantic Health System. Some of our affiliated websites and mobile apps, including, but not limited to [Private Health News](https://morristown.privatehealthnews.com/), are governed by their own separate privacy policies. Our Site may also contain links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by Atlantic Health System. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to carefully read the posted privacy statements of any website you access.

**PLEASE NOTE:** Atlantic Health System’s Notice of Privacy Practices is a separate document that governs how medical information about you may be used and disclosed by Atlantic Health System. You may access a copy of our Notice of Privacy Practices electronically at the link below, or upon request, you may obtain a paper copy by contacting our Privacy Officer at:

Privacy Officer  
Atlantic Health System, Inc.  
475 South Street, PO Box 1905  
Morristown, NJ 07962  
Telephone Phone: 973-660-3143

Notice of Privacy Practices >  
Aviso Sobre Practicas De Privacidad >

#### Types of Information We Collect

We may collect two types of information from you: **_Personal Information_** and **_Browsing Information._**

**1\. Personal Information.** The types of Personal Information that Atlantic Health System collects may include, among other things, the following categories of information (collectively, “Personal Information”):

  * Contact information (e.g., your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, password, and other login information);
  * Demographic information (e.g., date of birth, marital status);
  * Resume information (e.g., education, work and military history, legal work eligibility status);
  * Personal financial information, or other personal information that you choose to disclose to us.

In general, we do not collect Personal Information unless you choose to provide it. You are generally not required to submit any Personal Information to use our Site; however, you may be asked to provide Personal Information to gain access to some of our content. For example, you may choose to provide your contact information in order to receive information from us regarding our services or to register for an event.

**2\. Browsing Information.** Atlantic Health System may collect browsing and other technical information about you when you visit our Site. This may include, among other things, the following categories of information (collectively, “Browsing Information”):

  * Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, or device ID/UDID, protocol and sequence information;
  * Browser language and type;
  * Domain name system requirements;
  * Browsing history, such as time spent at a domain, time and date of your visit, and number of clicks;
  * http headers, application client and server banners;
  * Operating system and fingerprinting data;
  * Geolocation; and/or
  * Similar behavioral and usage information.

#### How Information is Collected and Used:

We may collect **Personal Information** about you from the following sources:

  * Information you provide through correspondence that you and others direct to us, for example email communications; 
  * Information we receive from you, or on your behalf, through information you submit on our Site;
  * Information we receive from your computer or mobile device;
  * Information we receive from our partners or service providers; and
  * Information we receive from other sources, as permitted by applicable laws, rules and regulations.

We may collect **Browsing information** and use such information as follows:

  * **Computer’s IP (Internet Protocol) address or browser type** : Our web server automatically collects the IP address of the computers that access our Site. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you access the Internet. We use this information to gather aggregate demographic information about our visitors, and we may use it to personalize the information you see on our Site and some of the electronic communications you receive from us.
  * **Pixel tracking** : A tracking pixel is a piece of code embedded on a web page of a website that collects information about a user’s engagement on that page. Tracking pixels may include a command to create cookies that can follow a user across different websites, including non-Atlantic Health System sites.
  * **Cookies** : A cookie is a small piece of data (i.e., text file) that can be stored on a user’s browser (on any type of device). Cookies may be placed on your device both by us and by third parties with whom we have a relationship, such as web analytic services and advertising network services. We use cookies to track certain information about you based upon your activity on our site or on a third party’s site. This information may include the URL that you just came from or which URL you go to next, what browser you are using, and your IP address. We use this information to better understand and serve visitors to our Site, and to enable us to deliver information tailored to your interests and preferences. We also use cookies in conjunction with certain applications (for example with our web security application) to allow you to easily move through secured pages once you have logged on. If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may be able to alter your browser’s configuration to refuse cookies.
  * **Aggregated Statistics** : We may collect statistics about the behavior of users on our Site. For instance, we may monitor the most popular forums on our Site. We may display this information publicly or provide it to others.
  * **Web Beacons** : Our Site may also contain electronic images known as Web Beacons (sometimes referred to as “clear gifs”). Web Beacons collect only limited information that includes a cookie number, time and date of page view, and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides. We may also carry Web Beacons placed by third party parties. These Web Beacons do not carry any personal information and are only used to track usage of our Site and activities associated with our Site, including but not limited to online features, services and/or programs offered.

**Google Analytics**. Like many websites, we also use **Google Analytics** to collect information about your use of our Site. This may include frequency of visitation, pages viewed and other sites visited prior to ours. Google sets cookies and may also read preexisting cookies to collect data from your web browser, such as the domain from which you access the Internet, the web address of the website from which you linked to our site, the time and date of your visit, the web pages that you view and click through, and your IP address. This information is stored on Google’s servers. Google uses this information to provide us with reports about traffic to our Site and your visit to our Site. [Find additional information on how Google Analytics collects and processes data >](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en)

Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics is governed by [Google’s Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). You may prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to the Site by disabling cookies on your browser or you may opt-out of our use of Google Analytics by [visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.) and installing the Google Analytics browser add-on.

**Retargeting and Remarketing**. We have also enabled additional Google Analytics Advertising Features: Google Display Network Impression Reporting and Remarketing. The Google Display Network Impression Reporting uses the Google Analytics cookies to track our ad impressions and your interactions with those impressions, including the effectiveness of those ads, which generates reports for us to help us analyze our advertisements. Remarketing with Google Analytics uses the Google Analytics and/or a third party cookie to serve advertisements to you across the Internet based on your visit to our Site. We also use the Google Ads service to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this Site. Google uses cookies (or other similar identifiers) to collect information about your visits to our Site and your interaction with our products and services to generate targeted advertisements to you on other sites that you visit across the Internet. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to our Site is restricted by [Google’s Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). You may opt out of the Google advertising cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). For additional information on Google Advertising, [review Google’s personalized advertising policies](https://support.google.com/adspolicy/answer/143465?hl=en&rd=2).

#### How We Use Personal and Browsing Information We Collect:

  * To improve our products and services that we perform for you;
  * To provide products and services to you;
  * To communicate with you and to inform you about Atlantic Health System’s and third parties’ products and services, jointly or independently;
  * To operate, evaluate, and improve Atlantic Health System’s operations, including but not limited to the operation of this Site.

If you have any questions or to opt-out of certain sharing of information, please let us know by sending your questions or requests to:

Atlantic Health System  

#### When Information is Disclosed:

If you participate on our Site by writing posts or responses, or importing a blog or other content, you should be aware that any information you choose to disclose on our Site can be read, collected, and used by other users of our Site. We are not responsible for information that you choose to submit to our Site and any forums therein. Your contributions may be searchable on our Site and some content on our Site may be public and searchable on the Internet. Even after you have closed your account or deleted information from your own profile, information you have shared with others or that others have copied may remain visible. Also, you may not be able to access, correct, or eliminate information about you that other Site users copied or exported out of our Site, because this information may not be in Atlantic Health System’s control. We may use comments, information or feedback that you may submit in any manner that we may choose without notice or compensation to you.

#### Third Party Information Sharing:

We might disclose Personal Information and/or Browsing Information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary: (1) to comply with a legal process, applicable laws, regulations and/or government requests; (2) to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or our Website Terms of Use; (3) to respond to claims that any materials, document, image, graphic, logo, design, audio, video or other information provided by you violates the rights of a third party; (4) in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of our assets; (5) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Atlantic Health System, its users or the public; or (6) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues relating to our Site.

We may provide Personal Information and/or Browsing Information to our affiliates and other businesses or persons for the purposes of (1) processing such information on our behalf; (2) providing services to you and on your behalf, and (3) promoting our services and the services of our affiliates and trusted business partners as permitted by applicable privacy law. Please note that the use of your information by an Atlantic Health System business partner may be subject to that party’s own privacy policy.

We may share Browsing Information with third parties to demonstrate the usage patterns for Atlantic Health System advertisements, content, functionality, promotions and/or services on our Site and to provide us with analytics services in connection with our Site.

Although certain third parties to whom we disclose Personal and/or Browsing Information are contractually bound to keep your information secure and private, we cannot guarantee the effectiveness of third party privacy policies and safety measures. 

#### How Long Do We Keep Your Information?

We may retain collected Personal Information and/or Browsing Information for an indefinite period of time. As described below, we have reasonable security measures in place to help protect the data that we collect and retain. However, no system can be completely secure, and we make no guarantees as to the safety or security of any information transmitted through our services.

#### Employment Opportunity Information:

For individuals interested in job opportunities with Atlantic Health System, our Site may allow prospective employees to request additional job opportunity information or submit a response to a job opportunity. Our Site may be used to collect Personal Information from prospective employees for human resources recruitment purposes. By submitting any of the foregoing information, you consent to its dissemination to, and use by, us and our affiliates. The foregoing also applies to job application inquiries that you may transmit to us other than through our Site. 

#### A Note to Parents and Legal Guardians:

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) governs how information is gathered online and how it is used when communication is received from children under the age of 13. Although Atlantic Health System is a non-commercial, nonprofit organization and is not subject to COPPA, we take children’s privacy and safety very seriously. 

We encourage parents to get involved with their children’s online usage and to provide guidance and be aware of personal information their children may be providing online. Our patient portal is available for use by children ages 12-17. Parents should be aware that this Privacy Policy will govern our use of Personal Information and Browsing Information, but also that information that is voluntarily given by children – or others – in email exchanges, bulletin boards, or the like may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited communications. We encourage all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use and disclosure of their Personal Information while using the Internet. 

If you are under the age of 13, please ask your parents to help you in using those parts of our Site that ask for Personal Information, and ask your parents for permission before you send any information about yourself (e.g., your name, address, email address, etc.) to Atlantic Health System or anyone else over the Internet, and before making any online purchases.

#### Privacy Outside Our Site:

Our Site may contain links to other websites, including links to third-party service providers. Atlantic Health System is not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any of those other websites. Please check with those websites in order to determine their privacy policies and your rights under them.

#### Our Site Security: 

We make every effort to ensure that information collected through our Site is not lost, misused or altered inappropriately by administering security measures. We maintain appropriate technical and organizational measures and safeguards to keep the Personal Information and Browsing Information that is disclosed to us secure. Firewalls are in place to prevent unauthorized access to our systems. A firewall controls traffic between the Internet and our internal network and protects your information stored within our systems from outsiders. Systems are monitored for suspicious activity to prevent any breaches in security. Any data provided by you sits behind this firewall; however, Atlantic Health System cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site. PLEASE NOTE THAT, BY ITS VERY NATURE, A WEBSITE CANNOT BE ABSOLUTELY PROTECTED AGAINST INTENTIONAL OR MALICIOUS INTRUSION ATTEMPTS. FURTHERMORE, ATLANTIC HEALTH SYSTEM DOES NOT CONTROL THE DEVICES OR COMPUTERS OR THE INTERNET OVER WHICH YOU MAY CHOOSE TO SEND CONFIDENTIAL PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND CANNOT, THEREFORE, PREVENT SUCH INTERCEPTIONS OR COMPROMISES TO YOUR INFORMATION WHILE IN TRANSIT TO ATLANTIC HEALTH SYSTEM. ATLANTIC HEALTH SYSTEM CANNOT AND DOES NOT GUARANTEE THE ABSOLUTE SECURITY OF ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS OR TRANSMISSIONS SINCE ANY TRANSMISSION MADE OVER THE INTERNET BY ANY ORGANIZATION OR INDIVIDUAL RUNS THE RISK OF INTERCEPTION. 

#### Do Not Track Signals:

Note that your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to websites and online services you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, Atlantic Health System does not alter its practices when it receives a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser.

#### Social Features:

Certain functionality on our Site is specially designed to permit interactions that you initiate between our Site and third party websites or services, including third party social networks (“Social Features”). Examples of Social Features include enabling you to transmit content to our Site from your account on a third party website or service, and to “like” or “share” our content on our Site to other websites or services.

If you choose to use Social Features, information you post or provide access to may be publicly displayed on our Site or by the provider of the Social Feature that you use. Similarly, if you post information on a third party platform that references Atlantic Health System (e.g., by using a hashtag associated with Atlantic Health System in a tweet or status update), your post may be published on our Site in accordance with the terms of the third party website or service. In addition, both Atlantic Health System and the third party may have access to certain information about you and your use of our Site and the third party site or service. We may also receive information about you if other users of a third party website give us access to their profiles and you are one of their “connections,” or information about you is otherwise accessible through your “connections” web pages, profile pages, or similar pages on a social networking or other third party website or interactive service. 

The information we collect in connection with Social Features is subject to this Privacy Policy. The information collected and stored by the third parties remains subject to those third parties’ privacy practices, including whether the third parties continue to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on those third party websites or services.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy:

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any updates to the Privacy Policy on our Site. Following any amendment of this Privacy Policy, your continued use of our Site, including but not limited to your disclosure of any information to us through the Site, will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms for all previously collected information and information collected from you in the future. 

_Last updated:_ August 16, 2018
